<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on AbdoulKaled</title>
    <link>https://gakas14.github.io/abdoulkaled_portfolio/portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on AbdoulKaled</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>©AbdoulKaled</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Aug 2021 19:47:09 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gakas14.github.io/abdoulkaled_portfolio/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>California House Price Prediction</title>
      <link>https://gakas14.github.io/abdoulkaled_portfolio/portfolio/project5/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Aug 2021 19:47:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gakas14.github.io/abdoulkaled_portfolio/portfolio/project5/</guid>
      <description>Build a model of housing prices to predict median house values in California using the provided dataset.
  Train the model to learn from the data to predict the median housing price in any district, given all the other metrics.
  Predict housing prices based on median_income and plot the regression chart for it.
  Link to GitHub</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Text Mining FIFAWorldCup2018</title>
      <link>https://gakas14.github.io/abdoulkaled_portfolio/portfolio/project3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 19:47:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gakas14.github.io/abdoulkaled_portfolio/portfolio/project3/</guid>
      <description>Python functions that accept a string and return N most frequent nouns (Take function name as “GetNMostFrequentNouns”) N most frequent verbs (Take function name as “GetNMostFrequentVerbs”) N most frequent delimiters (Take function name as “GetNMostFrequentDelimiters”) N most frequent prepositions (Take function name as “GetNMostFrequentPrepositions”) Run all the functions on the file “FIFAWorldCup2018.txt” and print the results. Python function that accepts a string and prints the first sentence in the string along with its syntax tree.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Car Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://gakas14.github.io/abdoulkaled_portfolio/portfolio/project4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2021 19:47:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gakas14.github.io/abdoulkaled_portfolio/portfolio/project4/</guid>
      <description>Predict the condition of a vehicle based on its features. Plot the most important features. Train multiple classifiers and compare the accuracy. Evaluate the XGBoost model with K-fold cross-validation.  Link to GitHub</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon Employee</title>
      <link>https://gakas14.github.io/abdoulkaled_portfolio/portfolio/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 19:47:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gakas14.github.io/abdoulkaled_portfolio/portfolio/project1/</guid>
      <description>Create a tool that predict the accuracy of the access status to certain resources of employees. Auto-access models seek to minimize human involvement.  Link to GitHub</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Health Insurance Cost</title>
      <link>https://gakas14.github.io/abdoulkaled_portfolio/portfolio/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 19:47:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gakas14.github.io/abdoulkaled_portfolio/portfolio/project2/</guid>
      <description> Find the correlation of every pair of features (and the outcome variable). Visualize the correlations using a heatmap. Normalize the inputs. Use the test data to find out the accuracy of the model. Visualize how the model uses the different features and which features have a greater effect.  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
